Joseph Stephen Cullinan Collection, 1895-1939
University of Houston Libraries
- Box List
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, May 1916 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, June1916 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Women's Organization for National Prohibition Reform, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Women's Organization for National Prohibition Reform, 1930-1932, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Concerning Anti-Prohibition Activities, 1930-1932, February - April, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Concerning Anti - Prohibition Activities, May - June, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Concerning Anti - Prohibition Activities, July 1933 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Concerning Anti - Prohibition Activities, August - December, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Concerning Anti - Prohibition Activities, 1934-1937 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Agricultural and Community Foundation, 1930-1931 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Concerning Agricultural Problems, 1921, 1926-1928 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence Concerning Agricultural Problems, 1929-1931 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence Concerning Unemployment Situation,, 1930, 1932-1933 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, N.R.A. Re - Employment Plan, 1933-1934 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence Concerning N.R.A., 1933-1935 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence Concerning N.R.A. in Iron and Steel Industries, January - July, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Concerning N.R.A. in Iron and Steel Industries, August - September, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Concerning N.R.A. in Iron and Steel Industries, October, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Concerning N.R.A. in Iron and Steel Industries, November - December, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Concerning N.R.A. in Iron and Steel Industries, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Shary Plan, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, "Back to the Land" Movement, 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, National Association of Community Councils, November - December, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Sentinels of the Republic, 1924-1930 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Sentinels of the Republic, 1931-1935 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Concerning Political Appointments, 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Concerning Political Appointments, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Concerning Political Appointments, 1934-1937 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Shadyside - Greenhouse, 1918-1920 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Shadyside Residence - Construction - Details, 1916-1919 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Shadyside Residence - Construction Details, 1916-1919 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Shadyside - Residence Construction - Details, 1918-1920 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Shadyside - Residence Construction - Details, 1918-1920 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Shadyside - Residence construction Details, 1918-1920 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Shadyside - Residence Construction Details, 1918-1920 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Shadyside - Residence Construction Details, 1916-1920 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Shadyside - Payment Receipts, 1917-1919 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Shadyside - Receipts, July-August, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Shadyside - Receipts, July-August, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Shadyside - Receipts, September-December, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Shadyside - Receipts, September-December, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Shadyside - Construction Materials, Orders, Receipts (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Shadyside - Construction Materials, Orders, Receipts (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Shadyside - Construction Materials, Orders, Receipts (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Shadyside -1916-1924 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Shadyside - 1916-1924 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Shadyside - trees, planting (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Shadyside - trees, planting (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Shadyside - specifications, prints, maps, and photos (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Shadyside - specifications, prints, maps, and photos (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1905,1906, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1915,1916, 1920-1922 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1925-1926 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1927-1929 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1928-1934 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, San Leon Company, 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, MacNider Property, 1915-1916 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Orange County, 1921-1923, 1926, 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Concerning Norsworthy Farm, December 1915-1916 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Concerning Property at Riske Crawford, 1919, 1920, 1927, 1928, 1930-1933 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, League to Enforce Peace, 1917-1920 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Interstate Inland Waterway League, 1914-1916 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, National Geographic Society, 1927-29, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, National Kindergarten Society, 1927-1936 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, National Association of Audubon Societies, 1924-1930 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, National Association of Audubon Societies, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Lotos Club, 1935-36 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, National Institute of Social Sciences, 1936-1937 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, National Economic League, 1923-1924, 1926, 1928, 1932-1933, 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Security Trust Company (Galveston), 1913-1919 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Panuco - Excelepor Oil Company, 1916-1917 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Park Place Company, 1915-1922 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Richland Quarry Company, 1915-1922 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Fidelity Trust Company of Houston Real Estate Dept, 1927, 1930, 1932, 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Fidelity Trust Company of Houston, Dec 1927-1929 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Fidelity Trust Company of Houston, 1930-1932 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Who's-Who, 1921, 1923, 1925-1927, 1929-1936 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Concerning Mexico, 1927-1935 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Tariff Policies, 1930-1932, 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Personal Mailing List, 1935-36 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Concerning Workmen's Insurance, 1925-1928 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Concerning Workmen's Insurance, 1929-1937 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Potash Industry, 1926, 1927, 1930, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Oscar Underwood Presidential Campaign, Nov-Dec 1923, Jan 1924 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Oscar Underwood Presidential Campaign, Feb-April 1924 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Concerning the Ku Klux Klan, 1922-1923 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Concerning the Ku Klux Klan, Jan-April 1924 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Concerning the Ku Klux Klan, May-Dec, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous Clubs and Organizations, 1927-1931, 1933-1934 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous Clubs and Organizations, 1935-1937 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Houston Art League, 1916-1924 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Museum of Fine Arts, 1925-1932, 1934-1936 and Clippings (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Mrs. Jane C. Sawyer (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Anna Cullinan (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Dr. M.P. Cullinan and Family (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Ms. Anna Cullinan (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Texas Avenue Project (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Crawford Street Paving (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Petroleum Industry, TX-, L434 (history); J.S.C. on Intl. policy in International Economic Relations, 1934; The "Houston Plan" Federal Housing Suburban Homes (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Tax Receipts (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Tax Receipts (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Tax Receipts (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Community Homestead Inc of Texas, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Community Homestead Inc of Texas, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Community Homestead Inc of Texas, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Community Homestead Inc of Texas, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, General Banking, 1920-27, 1930-1936 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Chemical National Bank, 1915-1925 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Chemical National Bank (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, national City Bank, 1921-1932 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Personal Accounts, 1916-1917 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Personal Accounts, 1924-29 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Personal Accounts, 1930-37 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Personal Photographs, 1916-1924 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Personal Photographs, 1925-1937 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Hotel and Train Reservations, 1924-1927 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Hotel and Train Reservations, 1928-1930 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Hotel and Train Reservations,1931-34 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Hotel and Train Reservations, 1935-37 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Condolence, 1920-21, 1923-26 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1916-21, 1924, 1926-28, 1932-33, 1935-36 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1926-29, 1931, 1932, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Books and Periodicals, 1930, 1931, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Books and Periodicals, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Craig Cullinan (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Craig Cullinan (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Craig Cullinan (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Craig Cullinan (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Frank Cullinan (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - John H. Cullinan (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - John H. Cullinan (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - John H. Cullinan (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - M.P. Cullinan (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Margaret Cullinan (Mrs. A.S. Wray) 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Margaret Cullinan (Mrs. A.S. Wray) 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mary Cullinan (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Nina Cullinan (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Nina Cullinan (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. J.S. Cullinan (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - J.S. Cullinan, Personal (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Investment Submitted, 1926-36 (1 of 3) (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Investment Submitted, 1926-36 (2 of 3) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Investment Submitted, 1926-36 (3 of 3) (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Reports (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Reports (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - City of Houston (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - City of Houston (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - City of Houston (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - City of Houston (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - City of Houston - Misc. (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - City of Houston - Misc. (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Automobiles (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (1 of 3) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (2 of 3) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (3 of 3) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Fidelity Trust Company (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Fidelity Trust Company (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Fidelity Trust Company (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Fidelity Trust Company (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Texas Company Securities, 1914-1921 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Securities, 1914-1916 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Central Petroleum Securities, 1915-18 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Central National Bank 1915-17 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Bills Payable, National City Bank of NY, 1916, 1918-20 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Commitments, 1915-1919 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Monthly Financial Forecasts, 1915-1919 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Personal Banking, 1918-36 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Bills Receivable, 1924-28, 1933-37 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Bills Payable, 1919-1931, 1936-37 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Liberty Bonds, 1919-1920 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Maya Corporation Notes, 1919-22, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Maya Corporation Notes, 1927-28, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Chemical National Bank, Texas Company Bonds and Stocks, 1914-15, 1917-19, 1920 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Personal Sundries, 1920-1923 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Personal Sundries, 1924-25, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Personal, 1924-27 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Personal, 1928-33 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Southern Steamship Houston, Philadelphia Route, 19 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Southern Steamship Houston, Philadelphia Route, 1919-20 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence concerning George Halm Loan, 1935-37 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- Elaine Arnold, 1933-1936 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Eureka Paving Company: Peculiarly Dated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Eureka Paving Company, 1914 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Eureka Paving Company, January 1915 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Eureka Paving Company, January 1915 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Eureka Paving Company, March 1915 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Eureka Paving Company, April 1915 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Eureka Paving Company, May 1915 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Eureka Paving Company, June 1915 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Eureka Paving Company, July 1915 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Eureka Paving Company, August 1915 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Eureka Paving Company, September 1915 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Eureka Paving Company, October 1915 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Eureka Paving Company, November 1915 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Eureka Paving Company, December 1915 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Eureka Paving Company, January 1916 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Eureka Paving Company, February 1916 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Eureka Paving Company, March 1916 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Eureka Paving Company, April 1916 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Eureka Paving Company, May 1916 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Eureka Paving Company, June 1916 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Eureka Paving Company, July 1916 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Eureka Paving Company, August 1916 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Eureka Paving Company, September 1916 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Eureka Paving Company, October 1916 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Eureka Paving Company, November 1916 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Eureka Paving Company, December 1916 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Eureka Paving Company, January 1917 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Eureka Paving Company, February 1917 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Eureka Paving Company, March 1917 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Eureka Paving Company, April 1917 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Eureka Paving Company, May 1917 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Eureka Paving Company, June 1917 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Eureka Paving Company, July 1917 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Eureka Paving Company, August 1917 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Eureka Paving Company, September 1917 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Eureka Paving Company, October 1917 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Eureka Paving Company, November 1917 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Eureka Paving Company, December 1917 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Eureka Paving Company, January 1918 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Eureka Paving Company, February 1918 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Eureka Paving Company, March 1918 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Eureka Paving Company, April 1918 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Eureka Paving Company, May 1918 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Eureka Paving Company, June 1918 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Eureka Paving Company, July 1918 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Eureka Paving Company, August 1918 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Eureka Paving Company, September 1918 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Eureka Paving Company, October 1918 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Eureka Paving Company, November 1918 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Eureka Paving Company, December 1918 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Eureka Paving Company, 1919-1922 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Magnolia Petroleum Co, 1918-33; Coffield and Muthrie (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Magnolia Petroleum Co, 1918-33; Coffield and Muthrie (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Highland Farm Corp. (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Highland Farm Corp. (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Highland Farm Corp. - Litigation (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Highland Farm Corp. - Litigation (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Highland Farm Corp. - Litigation (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Petroleum Building Co., 1925-26 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Petroleum Building Co., 1927-28 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Petroleum Building Co., 1929-36 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Petroleum Building Co., 1929-36 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Petroleum Building Co., 1929-37 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate Owned by JSC (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate Owned by JSC (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Carrington Property (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Carrington Property (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Liberty County Lands, 1921-1927 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Liberty County Lands, 1928-36 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Hill Street Property (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Montrose; Crawfrod and Rusk; Holbrook Property; Personal (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Freestone Count Lands (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Freestone Count Lands (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Freestone Count Lands (Cullinan, Sharp and others) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Freestone Count Lands (Cullinan, Sharp and others) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Sharp-Hughes Tool Company, 1913-14 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Sharp-Hughes Tool Company, 1915-16 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce - Equivalent Values, Correspondence 1916-1919 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce - Equivalent Values, Correspondence 1920 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce - Equivalent Values, Correspondence 1921-22, 1924-25 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce - Equivalent Values, Bureau of Labor Statistics Monthly Reports, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce - Equivalent Values, Bureau of Labor Statistics Monthly Reports, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce - Equivalent Values, Bureau of Labor Statistics Monthly Reports, 1923-24 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Texas Chamber of Commerce - 1914-15, 1917 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Texas Chamber of Commerce - 1919 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Texas Chamber of Commerce - 1920-21 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Texas Chamber of Commerce - Resolutions, 1919-1922 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Texas Business Men's Association, 1913-1914 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Material Concerning Suit Against Texas Business Men's Association, 1914-1915 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, "D-E" (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, "D" (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, "F" (1) (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, "F" (2) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, "P" (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, "P" (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, "Q-R" (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, "Q-R" (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, "R" (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, "R-S" (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, "R-S" (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, "S" (1 of 4) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, "S" (2 of 4) (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, "S" (3 of 4) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, "S" (4 of 4) (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, "T-V" (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, "W-Z" (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, "W-Z" (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence concerning Art Collecting (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence concerning Art Collecting (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Federal Investment Company, 1921-30 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Federal Investment Company,1931-33 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Federal Investment Company, 1934-37 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, 1914, 1915, Feb-June 1916 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Rice Institute, 1935-37 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Texas Industrial Congress, 1914-1916 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Texas Industrial Congress, 1917-1920 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, River Oaks Country Club, 1925-29, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Navy and marine Memorial, 1925-32 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Pennsylvania Society, 1916-1936 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, July-Nov 1916 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Texas Economic League, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Real Estate, 1915-1916 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Real Estate, 1919, 1920, 1922 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Real Estate, 1927-28 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Real Estate, 1929-37 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Real Estate Account Statements, 1936-1923 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Real Estate Account Statements, 1936-1923 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, concerning Northside Real Estate, 1928-31 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Houston Homes Inc, 1935-37 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Houston Homes Inc, 1935-37 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Houston Homes Inc, 1935-37 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Financial Statements, Houston Homes Inc, 1934-36 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Science League of America, 1926-32 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Social Service Federation, 1914-15 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Rocky Mountain Club of NY, 1928-1930 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Navy League of the United States, 1927-35 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Royal Society of the Arts, 1927-37 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Pan American Union, 1917-26 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Houston Country Club, 1935-36 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, 1925, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 28)